<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
	<ServerGroup Name="Romero Mod" Logo="" Description="">

		<Server Name="Romero Mod" Logo="">
			<Description>
			This is a mod I created to try out a few different things regarding code. I have tried to keep it as vanilla as possible, to maintain modlet compatibility, and just messed around with how zombie work.
			
			Features.
			- Zombies only take full damage from headshots.
			- Bloodmoons disabled.
			- Included Jax's Wilderness Spawn increase modlet (5x more zombies)
			- Added a difficulty tweaks mod to remove damage reduction from higher difficulties.
			- Removed zombie rage mode.
			- Added 10 slot toolbelt.
			- Added backpack stash buttons.
			- Added craftable log spikes.
			- Added ability to pick up plants with E.
			- Removed cop ability to puke.
			- Removed radiated vulture ability to puke.
			- Wandering hordes start from Day 2 at midnight.
			- Wandering horde frequency and zombie amount can now be configured by XML (1-RomeroModCore\Config\blocks.xml at the top)
			- Wandering horde configured to 30 zombies every 6 hours.
			- Added guppys PUSHABLE shopping cart (works like a bicycle for stam usage).
			- Added scrap iron arrows and arrow heads.
			- Added scrap club, scrap knuckles, scrap machete and scrap spear.
			- Added Pipe Pistol and Pipe Rifle.
			- Edited loot to remove stone arrows, leather knuckles, stone spear and wooden clubs from loot (replaced with scrap).
			- Edited loot to remove stone tools and replaced with scrap tools.
			- Moved iron tools, baseball bat, iron knuckles, iron spear and hunting knife from Level 1 of appropriate perk to Level 3 (localization updated to reflect this).
			- Scrap tools/weapons now locked behind schematics or level 1 of appropriate perk. (scrap arrows are NOT locked).
			- Increaed amount of XP required to level due to more zombies.
			- Increased dismemberment chance of explosives.

			7DTD Version Required: A20 Stable or 20.1 Experimental
			Current Mod Version: 2.0
			</Description>
			<EAC>Disabled</EAC>
			<DownloadMode>Clone</DownloadMode>
			<Version>Latest</Version>
			<ReleaseNotes>https://community.7daystodie.com/topic/21581-romero-mod-a-game-modesuite-of-zombie-tweaks/</ReleaseNotes>
			<Downloads>
				<Download>https://github.com/KhaineGB/RomeroModA20/archive/refs/heads/main.zip</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>	
	</ServerGroup>
</Servers>


